<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="jesus_prayer">
        <item>The Chaplet of Divine Mercy</item>
        <item>Act of consecration to the sacrad Heart of Jesus</item>
        <item>Prayer to the Sacrad Heart</item>
        <item>Before a Crucifix</item>
        <item>Anima Christi</item>
        <item>Divine Praises</item>
        <item>Chaplet of the Precious Blood</item>
        <item>Litany of the Infant Jesus</item>
        <item>The JESUS prayer</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="list_of_jesus_prayers">
        <item>\t\t <b>Make the Sign of the Cross</b>
<b>
St. Faustina\’s Prayer for Sinners</b>\n
O Jesus, eternal Truth, our Life, I call upon You and I beg Your mercy for poor sinners. O sweetest Heart of my Lord, full of pity and unfathomable mercy,
            I plead with You for poor sinners. O Most Sacred Heart, Fount of Mercy from which gush forth rays of inconceivable graces upon the entire human race,
            I beg of You light for poor sinners.
            O Jesus, be mindful of Your own bitter Passion and do not permit the loss of souls redeemed at so dear a price of Your most precious Blood.
            O Jesus, when I consider the great price of Your Blood, I rejoice at its immensity, for one drop alone would have been enough for the salvation of all sinners.
            Although sin is an abyss of wickedness and ingratitude, the price paid for us can never be equalled. Therefore, let every soul trust in the Passion of the Lord,
            and place its hope in His mercy. God will not deny His mercy to anyone. Heaven and earth may change, but God\'s mercy will never be exhausted.
            Oh, what immense joy burns in my heart when I contemplate Your incomprehensible goodness,
            O Jesus! I desire to bring all sinners to Your feet that they may glorify Your mercy throughout endless ages.

            \n
            You expired, Jesus, but the source of life gushed forth for souls, and the ocean of mercy opened up for the whole world. O Fount of Life,
            unfathomable Divine Mercy, envelop the whole world and empty Yourself out upon us.

<b>(Repeat three times)</b>\n
O Blood and Water, which gushed forth from the Heart of Jesus as a fount of mercy for us, I trust in You!
\n\n
 <b>Our Father</b>\n
Our Father, Who art in heaven, hallowed be Thy name; Thy kingdom come; Thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.\n Give us this day our daily bread;
            and forgive us our trespasses as we forgive those who trespass against us; and lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil, Amen.
\n\n
            <b>Hail Mary</b>\n
Hail Mary, full of grace. The Lord is with thee. Blessed art thou amongst women, and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.\n
            Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners, now and at the hour of our death, Amen.
\n\n
 <b>The Apostles\’ Creed</b>\n
I believe in God, the Father almighty, Creator of heaven and earth, and in Jesus Christ, His only Son, our Lord, who was conceived by the Holy Spirit,
            born of the Virgin Mary, suffered under Pontius Pilate, was crucified, died and was buried;
            He descended into hell; on the third day He rose again from the dead;
            He ascended into heaven, and is seated at the right hand of God the Father almighty; from there He will come to judge the living and the dead. \n
            I believe in the Holy Spirit, the holy catholic Church, the communion of saints, the forgiveness of sins,
            the resurrection of the body, and life everlasting. Amen.
        \n\n
    <b>The Eternal Father</b>\n
    Eternal Father, I offer you the Body and Blood, Soul and Divinity of Your Dearly Beloved Son,
            Our Lord, Jesus Christ, in atonement for our sins and those of the whole world.
    \n\n
            <b>On the 10 Small Beads of Each Decade</b>\n
    For the sake of His sorrowful Passion, have mercy on us and on the whole world.
    \n\n
            <b>Repeat for the remaining decades</b>\n
        Saying the \"Eternal Father\" (6) on the \"Our Father\" bead and then 10 \"For the sake of His sorrowful Passion\"
            (7) on the following \"Hail Mary\" beads.
    \n\n
             <b>Conclude with Holy God (Repeat three times)</b>\n
    Holy God, Holy Mighty One, Holy Immortal One, have mercy on us and on the whole world.
        \n\n
    <b>Optional Closing Prayers</b>\n
            Eternal God, in whom mercy is endless and the treasury of compassion — inexhaustible, look kindly upon us and increase Your mercy in us,
            that in difficult moments we might not despair nor become despondent, but with great confidence submit ourselves to Your holy will,
            which is Love and Mercy itself.

        O Greatly Merciful God, Infinite Goodness, today all mankind calls out from the abyss of its misery to Your mercy — to Your compassion, O God;
            and it is with its mighty voice of misery that it cries out. Gracious God, do not reject the prayer of this earth\'s exiles!
            O Lord, Goodness beyond our understanding, Who are acquainted with our misery through and through, and know that by our own power we cannot ascend to You,
            we implore You: anticipate us with Your grace and keep on increasing Your mercy in us,
            that we may faithfully do Your holy will all through our life and at death\'s hour.
            Let the omnipotence of Your mercy shield us from the darts of our salvation\’s enemies, that we may with confidence,
            as Your children, await Your [Son\’s] final coming —
            that day known to You alone. And we expect to obtain everything promised us by Jesus in spite of all our wretchedness.
            For Jesus is our Hope: through His merciful Heart,
            as through an open gate, we pass through to heaven. Amen</item>


        <item>\t\tO Sacred Heart of Jesus, to Thee I consecrate and offer up my person and my life, my actions, trials, and sufferings,
            that my entire being may henceforth only be employed in loving, honoring and glorifying Thee. This is my irrevocable will, to belong entirely to Thee,
            and to do all for Thy love, renouncing with my whole heart all that can displease Thee.

        I take Thee, O Sacred Heart, for the sole object of my love, the protection of my life, the pledge of my salvation, the remedy of my frailty and inconstancy,
            the reparation for all the defects of my life, and my secure refuge at the hour of my death. Be Thou, O Most Merciful Heart, my justification before God Thy Father,
            and screen me from His anger which I have so justly merited. I fear all from my own weakness and malice, but placing my entire confidence in Thee,
            O Heart of Love, I hope all from Thine infinite Goodness.
            Annihilate in me all that can displease or resist Thee. Imprint Thy pure love so deeply in my heart that I may never forget Thee or be separated from Thee.
        I beseech Thee, through Thine infinite Goodness, grant that my name be engraved upon Thy Heart, for in this I place all my happiness and all my glory,
            to live and to die as one of Thy devoted servants. Amen.</item>

        <item>\t\tO most holy heart of Jesus, fountain of every blessing, I adore you, I love you, and with lively sorrow for my sins I offer you this poor heart of mine.
            Make me humble, patient, pure and wholly obedient to your will. Grant, Good Jesus, that I may live in you and for you. Protect me in the midst of danger.
            Comfort me in my afflictions. Give me health of body, assistance in my temporal needs, your blessing on all that I do, and the grace of a holy death. Amen.</item>
        <item>\t\tLook down upon me, good and gentle Jesus
while before Your face I humbly kneel and,
with burning soul,
pray and beseech You
to fix deep in my heart lively sentiments
of faith, hope, and charity;
true contrition for my sins,
and a firm purpose of amendment.
\n\n
While I contemplate,
with great love and tender pity,
Your five most precious wounds,
pondering over them within me
and calling to mind the words which David,
Your prophet, said to You, my Jesus:
\n\n
            \"They have pierced My hands and My feet,
they have numbered all My bones.\"

Amen.</item>
        <item>\t\tSoul of Christ, sanctify me.\n
Body of Christ, save me.\n
Blood of Christ, inebriate me.\n
Water from the side of Christ, wash me.\n
Passion of Christ, strengthen me.\n
O Good Jesus, hear me.\n
Within your wounds hide me.\n
Permit me not to be separated from you.\n
From the wicked foe, defend me.\n
At the hour of my death, call me
and bid me come to you\n
That with your saints I may praise you
For ever and ever. Amen.</item>
        <item>\t\t\Blessed be God.\n
Blessed be His Holy Name.\n
Blessed be Jesus Christ, true God and true Man.\n
Blessed be the Name of Jesus.\n
Blessed be His Most Sacred Heart.\n
Blessed be His Most Precious Blood.\n
Blessed be Jesus in the Most Holy Sacrament of the Altar.\n
Blessed be the Holy Spirit, the Paraclete.\n
Blessed be the great Mother of God, Mary most Holy.\n
Blessed be her Holy and Immaculate Conception.\n
Blessed be her Glorious Assumption.\n
Blessed be the name of Mary, Virgin and Mother.\n
Blessed be St. Joseph, her most chaste spouse.\n
Blessed be God in His Angels and in His Saints. Amen.</item>
        <item>\t\t
<b>Invocation of the Holy Spirit</b>\n
Come, Holy Spirit, fill the hearts of Your faithful and kindle in them the fire of Your love.\n
L: Send forth Your Spirit and they shall be created.\n
R: And You shall renew the face of the earth.\n\n

            <b>Let us Pray</b>\n
O God, Who did teach the hearts of the faithful by the light of the Holy Spirit, grant us by the same Spirit to be truly wise and ever rejoice in His consolations,
            through Christ Our Lord. Amen.
\n
            <b>Apostles Creed
(Bow Your Head)</b>
\n\n
May the Precious Blood that pours out from the Sacred Head of Our Lord Jesus Christ, the Temple of Divine Wisdom,
            Tabernacle of Divine Knowledge and Sunshine of heaven and earth, cover us now and forever. Amen.
\n L: O most Precious Blood of Jesus Christ.\n
R: Heal the wounds in the most Sacred Heart of Jesus.
\n\n
            <b>Our Father(3) </b>\n
            <b>Hail Mary(3)</b>\n
            <b>Glory Be</b>
            <i>(Bow Your Head)</i>\n\n
May the Precious Blood that pours out from the Sacred Head of Our Lord Jesus Christ, the Temple of Divine Wisdom,
            Tabernacle of Divine Knowledge and Sunshine of heaven and earth, cover us now and forever. Amen.
\n\n
            <b>THE FIRST MYSTERY\n
            The Nailing of the Right Hand of Our Lord Jesus </b><i>(Pause for brief meditation)</i>\n
By the precious wound in Your right hand and through the pain of the nail which pierced Your right hand,
            may the Precious Blood that pours out from there save sinners of the whole world and convert many souls. Amen.
\n\n
L: O most Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
R: Heal the wounds in the most Sacred Heart of Jesus.\n

            <b>Our Father</b>
            \n<b>Hail Mary</b>\n
L: Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
            R: Save us and the whole world. <i>(12 times)</i>\n\n

            <b>Glory Be</b>
            <i>(Bow Your Head)</i>\n
May the Precious Blood that pours out from the Sacred Head of Our Lord Jesus Christ, the Temple of Divine Wisdom,
            Tabernacle of Divine Knowledge and Sunshine of heaven and earth, cover us now and forever. Amen.
\n\n
            <b>THE SECOND MYSTERY
\n
The Nailing of the Left Hand of
Our Lord Jesus</b>
            <i>(Pause for brief meditation)</i>\n
By the precious wound in Your left hand and through the pain of the nail which pierced Your left hand,
            may the Precious Blood that pours out from there save souls in Purgatory and protect the dying against the attack of infernal spirits. Amen.
            \n L: O most Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
R: Heal the wounds in the most Sacred Heart of Jesus\n

            <b>Our Father \n Hail Mary</b>
L: Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
            R: Save us and the whole world. <i>(12 times)</i>

            <b>Glory Be</b>
            <i>(Bow Your Head)</i>\n
May the Precious Blood that pours out from the Sacred Head of Our Lord Jesus Christ, the Temple of Divine Wisdom,
            Tabernacle of Divine Knowledge and Sunshine of heaven and earth, cover us now and forever. Amen.
\n\n

            <b>THE THIRD MYSTERY\n

The Nailing of the Right Foot of
                Our Lord Jesus</b><i>(Pause for brief meditation)</i>\n
By the precious wound in Your right foot and through the pain of the nail which pierced Your right foot,
            may the Precious Blood that pours out from there cover the foundation of the Catholic Church against the plans of the occult kingdom and evil men. Amen.
\n
L: O most Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
R: Heal the wounds in the most Sacred Heart of Jesus.\n

<b>Our Father \nHail Mary</b>\n

L: Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
            R: Save us and the whole world. <i>(12 times)</i>\n
            <b>Glory Be</b>
            <i>(Bow Your Head)</i>\n
May the Precious Blood that pours out from the Sacred Head of Our Lord Jesus Christ, the Temple of Divine Wisdom,
            Tabernacle of Divine Knowledge and Sunshine of heaven and earth, cover us now and forever. Amen.
\n\n
            <b>
THE FOURTH MYSTERY
\n
The Nailing of the Left Foot of Our Lord Jesus</b>

<i>(Pause for brief meditation)</i>\n
By the precious wound in Your left foot, and through the pain of the nail which pierced Your left foot,
            may the Precious Blood that pours out from there protect us in all our ways against the plans and the attacks of evil spirits and their agents. Amen.
\n
L: O most Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
R: Heal the wounds in the most Sacred Heart of Jesus.\n
\n
            <b>Our Father \nHail Mary</b>
\n
L: Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
            R: Save us and the whole world. <i>(12 times)</i>
            \n
            <b>Glory Be</b>
            <i>(Bow Your Head)</i>\n
May the Precious Blood that pours out from the Sacred Head of Our Lord Jesus Christ, the Temple of Divine Wisdom,
            Tabernacle of Divine Knowledge and Sunshine of heaven and earth, cover us now and forever. Amen.
\n\n
            <b>
THE FIFTH MYSTERY\n

The Piercing of the Sacred Side of
Our Lord Jesus</b>
            <i>(Pause for brief meditation)</i>\n
By the precious wound in Your Sacred Side and through the pain of the lance which pierced Your Sacred Side,
            may the Precious Blood and water that pour out from there cure the sick, raise the dead,
            solve our present problems and teach us the way to our God for eternal glory. Amen.
\n
L: O most Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
R: Heal the wounds in the most Sacred Heart of Jesus.\n

            <b>Our Father</b>\n
            <b>Hail Mary</b>\n

L: Precious Blood of Jesus Christ\n
            R: Save us and the whole world. <i>(12 times)</i>\n\n

            <b>Glory Be</b>
            <i>(Bow Your Head)</i>\n\n
May the Precious Blood that pours out from the Sacred Head of Our Lord Jesus Christ, the Temple of Divine Wisdom,
            Tabernacle of Divine Knowledge and Sunshine of heaven and earth, cover us now and forever. Amen.
L: O most Precious Blood of Jesus Christ
R: Heal the wounds in the most Sacred Heart of Jesus. (repeat 3 times)

<b>Hail Holy Queen</b>
\n
Let us Pray\n
O most Precious Blood of Jesus Christ, we honor, worship and adore You because of Your work of the everlasting covenant that brings peace to mankind.
            Heal the wounds in the most Sacred Heart of Jesus. Console the Almighty Father on His throne and wash away the sins of the whole world.
            May all revere You,
            O Precious Blood, have mercy. Amen.
\n\n
Most Sacred Heart of Jesus \nhave mercy on us
Immaculate Heart of Mary \npray for us
St. Joseph, husband of Mary \npray for us
Saints Peter and Paul \npray for us
St. John at the foot of the Cross \npray for us
St. Mary Magdalene \npray for us
All the prayer warriors and intercessors of heaven \npray for us
All the great saints of Our Lord \npray for us
All the heavenly hosts, Legion of Mary \npray for us
            \n\n
\"Be humble and accept the Divine Will, you will reach the end. Offer your families to My Precious Blood. I will save them.
            I promise to convert them before the Great Tribulation comes. There will be peace and love. I say to you adore and honor My Precious Blood.\"

\"I will allow My Precious Blood to fall on the heart of every sinner offered to My Precious Blood.
            I say to you offer to Me and pray for them always through My Precious Blood. I will destroy all evils in your families. I have heard your prayers.
            Rejoice, for your request has been granted.\"

\"My children, never fail to give testimony when you see this goodness, from the One who loves thee. If anyone among you loves Me,
            let him console Me and pray for unrepented sinners, the remaining days are great and holy. Your adoration will be great and holy.
            Come with reverence and awe and worship your God.\"</item>

        <item>\t\tLord, have mercy on us, <i>Lord, have mercy on us.</i>\n
            Christ, have mercy on us, <i>Christ, have mercy on us.</i>\n
Lord, have mercy on us, <i>Lord, have mercy on us.</i>\n
            Jesus, hear us.  <i>Jesus, graciously hear us.</i>\n
            God the Father of Heaven,  <i>Have mercy on us. </i>\n
God the Son, Redeemer of the world,  <i>Have mercy on us. </i>\n
God the Holy Spirit,  <i>Have mercy on us. </i> \n
Holy Trinity, One God,  <i>Have mercy on us. </i> \n
\n\n
            Infant, Jesus Christ, <i>have mercy on us.</i>\n
Infant, true God, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Son of the living God, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Son of the Virgin Mary, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, strong in weakness, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, powerful in tenderness, <i>have mercy on us.</i>\n
Infant, Treasure of grace, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Fountain of love, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Renewer of the heavens, <i>have mercy on us.</i>.\n
Infant, Repairer of the evils of the earth, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Head of the angels, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Root of the patriarchs, <i>have mercy on us.</i>\n
Infant, Speech of the prophets, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Desire of the Gentiles, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Joy of shepherds, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Light of the Magi, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Salvation of infants, <i>have mercy on us.</i>\n
Infant, Expectation of the just, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, Instructor of the wise, <i>have mercy on us.</i> \n
Infant, First-fruit of all saints, <i>have mercy on us.</i>\n
\n
            Be merciful, <i>spare us, O Infant Jesus.</i> \n
            Be merciful, <i>graciously hear us, O Infant Jesus.</i>\n
\n\n

            From the slavery of the children of Adam, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
From the slavery of the devil, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
From the evil desires of the flesh, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
From the malice of the world, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
From the pride of life, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>.\n
From the inordinate desire of knowing, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
From blindness of spirit, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
From an evil will, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
From our sins, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy most pure Conception, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy most humble Nativity, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy tears, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy most painful Circumcision, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy most glorious Epiphany, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy most pious Presentation, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy most divine life, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy poverty, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy many sufferings, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
Through Thy labors and travels, <i>Infant Jesus, deliver us.</i>\n
\n
            Lamb of God, Who takes away the sins of the world,  <i>Have mercy on us, O Infant Jesus.</i> \n
            Lamb of God, Who takes away the sins of the world,  <i>Graciously hear us, O Infant Jesus.</i> \n
            Lamb of God, Who takes away the sins of the world,  <i>Have mercy on us.</i> \n
\n
Jesus, Infant, hear us. Jesus, Infant, graciously hear us.</item>
        <item>\t\tLord Jesus Christ, Son of God, have mercy on me, a sinner.</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>