<resources>
  <string-array name="order_of_mass">
    <item>THE INTRODUCTORY RITE</item>
    <item>THE LITURGY OF THE WORD</item>
    <item>THE LITURGY OF THE HOLY EUCHARIST</item>
    <item>THE COMMUNION RITE</item>
    <item>THE CONCLUDING RITE</item>
  </string-array>

  <string-array name="order_of_mass_contents">
    <item>SIGN OF THE CROSS\n
All make the Sign of the Cross as the Priest says.\n

In the name of the Father, and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit.
The people reply:

Amen.\n\n
GREETING\n
Then the Priest greets the people:\n

Either: The grace of our Lord Jesus Christ,
and the love of God,
and the communion of the Holy Spirit
be with you all.\n
Or: Grace to you and peace from God our Father
and the Lord Jesus Christ.\n
Or: The Lord be with you.\n\n
The people reply\n

And with your spirit.\n\n
The Priest, or a Deacon, or another minister, may very briefly introduce the faithful to the Mass of the day.
\n\n\n
PENITENTIAL ACT\n\n
The Priest invites the faithful to the Penitential Act.\n\n

Brethren (brothers and sisters), let us acknowledge our sins,
and so prepare ourselves to celebrate the sacred mysteries.\n\n
A brief pause for silence follows, and then one of the following Penitential Acts:
        \n\n
A. I confess to almighty God…\n
All say:
\n
I confess to almighty God
and to you, my brothers and sisters,
that I have greatly sinned,
in my thoughts and in my words,
in what I have done and in what I have failed to do,
And, striking their breast, they say:

through my fault,
through my fault,
through my most grievous fault;
therefore I ask blessed Mary ever-Virgin,
all the Angels and Saints,
and you, my brothers and sisters,
to pray for me to the Lord our God.\n\n
The absolution by the Priest follows:\n\n

May almighty God have mercy on us,
forgive us our sins,
and bring us to everlasting life.
Amen.\n\n
The Kyrie
The Kyrie, eleison (Lord, have mercy) invocations may follow:
\n\n
V. Lord, have mercy.\n
R. Lord, have mercy.\n
V. Christ, have mercy.\n
R. Christ, have mercy.\n
V. Lord, have mercy.\n
R. Lord, have mercy.\n
        \n
Or:\n

V. Kyrie, eleison.\n
R. Kyrie, eleison.\n
V. Christe, eleison.\n
R. Christe, eleison.\n
V. Kyrie, eleison.\n
R. Kyrie, eleison.\n\n
Gloria
\n
Glory to God in the highest,
and on earth peace to people of good will.
We praise you,
we bless you,
we adore you,
we glorify you,
we give you thanks for your great glory,
Lord God, heavenly King,
O God, almighty Father.
Lord Jesus Christ, Only Begotten Son,
Lord God, Lamb of God, Son of the Father,
you take away the sins of the world,
have mercy on us;
you take away the sins of the world,
receive our prayer;
you are seated at the right hand of the Father,
have mercy on us.
For you alone are the Holy One,
you alone are the Lord,
you alone are the Most High,
Jesus Christ,
with the Holy Spirit,
in the glory of God the Father.
Amen.\n\n

The Priest says:
\n\n
Let us pray.
\nAnd all pray in silence with the Priest for a while. Then the Priest says the Collect prayer, at the end of which the people acclaim:

Amen.</item>
    <item>
        By hearing the word proclaimed in worship, the faithful again enter into the unending dialogue between God and the covenant people, a dialogue sealed in the sharing of the Eucharistic food and drink. The proclamation of the word is thus integral to the Mass and at its very centre. It is appropriate to have a brief time of quiet after the readings for those present to take the word of God to heart and begin to prepare a prayerful response to what they have heard.
\n
All sit
\n\n
First Reading\n
To indicate the end of these readings, the reader acclaims:
\n
The word of the Lord.\n\n
All reply:\n
Thanks be to God.\n\n
Psalm\n
After the First Reading the psalmist or cantor sings or says the Psalm, with the people making the response.
\n\n
Second Reading\n
On Sundays and certain other days there is a second reading. It concludes with the same responsory as above.
\n\n
Gospel\n
The assembly stands to sing the Gospel Acclamation to welcome the Gospel. They remain standing in honour of the Gospel reading, the high point of the Liturgy of the Word. \n\n
        At the ambo the Deacon, or the Priest says:
\n
The Lord be with you.\n\n
The people reply:
\n
And with your spirit.\n
The Deacon, or the Priest:
\n
A reading from the holy Gospel according to N.\n\n
He makes the Sign of the Cross on the book and, together with the people, on his forehead, lips, and breast. At the same time the people acclaim:
\n\n
Glory to you, O Lord.\n\n
At the end of the Gospel, the Deacon, or the Priest, acclaims:
\n
The Gospel of the Lord.\n\n
All reply:\n
Praise to you, Lord Jesus Christ.\n\n
After the proclamation of the Gospel the congregation is seated.
\n
The Homily.
At the end of the Homily it is appropriate for there to be a brief silence for recollection. The congregation then stands.
\n\n
The Creed\n
On Sundays and Solemnities, the Profession of Faith or Creed will follow. During Lent and Easter Time, especially, the Apostles’ Creed may be used.
        \n\n
I believe in one God,
the Father almighty,
maker of heaven and earth,
of all things visible and invisible.
I believe in one Lord Jesus Christ,
the Only Begotten Son of God,
born of the Father before all ages.
God from God,
Light from Light,
true God from true God,
begotten, not made, consubstantial with the Father;
through him all things were made.
For us men and for our salvation he came down from heaven,
At the words that follow, up to and including ‘and became man’, all bow.
and by the Holy Spirit was incarnate of the Virgin Mary,
and became man.
For our sake he was crucified under Pontius Pilate,
he suffered death and was buried,
and rose again on the third day
in accordance with the Scriptures.
He ascended into heaven
and is seated at the right hand of the Father.
He will come again in glory
to judge the living and the dead
and his kingdom will have no end.
I believe in the Holy Spirit, the Lord, the giver of life,
who proceeds from the Father and the Son,
who with the Father and the Son is adored and glorified,
who has spoken through the prophets.
I believe in one, holy, catholic and apostolic Church.
I confess one Baptism for the forgiveness of sins
and I look forward to the resurrection of the dead
and the life of the world to come. Amen.\n\n

The Prayer of the Faithful (Bidding Prayers)\n
After each intention there is a pause while the faithful pray. The minister says:
\n
Lord, in your mercy.\n\n
All reply:\n

Hear our prayer.\n\n
The Priest concludes the Prayer with a collect. When the Liturgy of the Word has been completed, the people sit.
    </item>
      <item>
      \"After the priest concludes all personal preparatory rites, all stand\"\n\n
Pray, brethren (brothers and sisters),
that my sacrifice and yours
may be acceptable to God,
the almighty Father.\n\n
The people reply:\n

May the Lord accept the sacrifice at your hands
for the praise and glory of his name,
for our good
and the good of all his holy Church.\n\n
Then the Priest says the Prayer over the Offerings, at the end of which the people acclaim:
\n
Amen.\n\n
THE EUCHARISTIC PRAYER\n\n
Extending his hands, the Priest says:\n

Priest: The Lord be with you.\n\n
People: And with your spirit.\n\n
      Priest, raising his hands, continues: Lift up your hearts.\n\n
People: We lift them up to the Lord.\n\n
 Priest, with hands extended, adds: Let us give thanks to the Lord our God.\n\n
 People: It is right and just.\n
\n
      HOLY, HOLY, HOLY
      \n\n
Holy, Holy, Holy Lord God of hosts.
Heaven and earth are full of your glory.
Hosanna in the highest.
Blessed is he who comes in the name of the Lord.
Hosanna in the highest.
After the singing of the Sanctus the congregation kneels for the remainder of the Eucharistic Prayer.
      \n\n

THE MYSTERY OF FAITH\n\n
The people continue, acclaiming:
      \n

Either:
We proclaim your Death, O Lord,
and profess your Resurrection
until you come again.\n
Or:\n
When we eat this Bread and drink this Cup,
we proclaim your Death, O Lord,
until you come again.\n
Or:\n
Save us, Saviour of the world,
for by your Cross and Resurrection
you have set us free.\n\n
Then the Priest alone continues:
After concluding the prayer, he says:
Through him, and with him, and in him,
O God, almighty Father,
in the unity of the Holy Spirit,
all glory and honour is yours,
for ever and ever.
Amen.
    </item>


    <item>THE LORD\'S PRAYER\n
The congregation stands and the Priest says:

At the Saviour’s command
and formed by divine teaching, we dare to say:\n
Together with the people, he continues:
\n\n
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name;
thy kingdom come,
thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those who trespass against us;
and lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.\n\n
The Priest alone continues, saying:
\n
Deliver us, Lord, we pray, from every evil,
graciously grant peace in our days,
that, by the help of your mercy,
we may be always free from sin
and safe from all distress,
as we await the blessed hope
and the coming of our Saviour, Jesus Christ.\n\n
The people conclude the prayer, acclaiming:
For the kingdom,
the power and the glory are yours
now and for ever.\n\n

Then the Priest alone says aloud:
Lord Jesus Christ,
who said to your Apostles:
Peace I leave you, my peace I give you,
look not on our sins,
but on the faith of your Church,
and graciously grant her peace and unity
in accordance with your will.
Who live and reign for ever and ever.\n\n
The people reply:
Amen.\n\n
The Priest adds:
The peace of the Lord be with you always.\n
The people reply:
And with your spirit.\n
The Deacon, or the Priest, adds:
Let us offer each other the sign of peace.\n\n
And all offer one another the customary sign of peace: a handclasp or handshake, which is an expression of peace, communion, and charity.\n\n
Breaking of the Bread
During the breaking of the host the following is sung or said:
\n\n

Lamb of God, you take away the sins of the world,\n
have mercy on us.\n
Lamb of God, you take away the sins of the world,\n
have mercy on us.\n
Lamb of God, you take away the sins of the world,
\ngrant us peace.\n\n
After the Lamb of God, the people kneel.
\n\n
Invitation to Communion\n
After his private prayers of preparation the Priest genuflects, takes the host and, holding it slightly raised above the paten or above the chalice says aloud:
\n\n
Behold the Lamb of God,
behold him who takes away the sins of the world.
Blessed are those called to the supper of the Lamb.\n\n
And together with the people he adds once:\n
Lord, I am not worthy
that you should enter under my roof,
but only say the word and my soul shall be healed.\n\n
COMMUNION\n
After the priest has reverently consumed the Body and Blood of Christ the communicants come forward in reverent procession, and make a preparatory act of reverence by bowing their head in honour of Christ’s presence in the Sacrament. They receive Holy Communion standing. The Priest says:
\n
The Body (Blood) of Christ.\n
The communicant replies:
Amen.\n\n
 After Communion, the Priest says:
\n
Let us pray.\n
All stand and pray in silence. Then the Priest says the Prayer after Communion, at the end of which the people acclaim:

Amen.</item>
    <item>
Blessing
The Priest says:
The Lord be with you.\n\n
The people reply:
And with your spirit.\n\n
The Priest blesses the people, saying:
May almighty God bless you,
the Father, and the Son, and the Holy Spirit.\n\n
The people reply:
Amen.
        \n\n
DISMISSAL\n\n
Then the Deacon, or the Priest himself, says:

Either: Go forth, the Mass is ended.\n
Or: Go and announce the Gospel of the Lord.\n
Or: Go in peace, glorifying the Lord by your life.\n
Or: Go in peace.\n\n
The people reply:

Thanks be to God.</item>
  </string-array>

</resources>