<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="sacrament">
        <item>Introduction</item>
        <item>Baptism</item>
        <item>Confirmation</item>
        <item>Holy Eucharist</item>
        <item>Penance</item>
        <item>Anointing of the sick</item>
        <item>Holy Order</item>
        <item>Holy Matrimony</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_of_sacrament_facts">
        <item>jsm khjasa</item>
        <item>
            Baptism is a sacrament which cleanses us from original sin, makes us christians, children of God and members of the church\n\n
Baptism is the first sacrament where you become united with Christ and the Church – no other sacrament can be received without it.
            A priest performs this rite by immersing the baptismal candidate into water, therefore cleansing their original sin through water and the word.
            The candidate traditionally wears white garments, a candle is lit and they are anointed with sacred chrism.
            This is the first step in your relationship with God and Christ. Usually this takes place when the candidate is a baby, however,
            it\’s never too late and you\’re never too old to begin your journey with God.
            It\’s common to have a baptism celebration with friends and family afterwards and give the child baptism keepsakes that will help them grow in their faith.
        \n\n
        Go therefore and make disciples of all the nations, baptizing them in the name of the Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit. Matthew 28:19 \n\n
And it came to pass in those days, that Jesus came from Nazareth of Galilee, and was baptized of John in Jordan.
            And straightway coming up out of the water, he saw the heavens opened, and the Spirit like a dove descending upon him:
            And there came a voice from heaven, saying, Thou art my beloved Son, in whom I am well pleased. Mark 1:9-11\n\n
And they said, Believe on the Lord Jesus Christ, and thou shalt be saved, and thy house. And he took them the same hour of the night, and washed their stripes; and was baptized, he and all his, straightway. Acts 16:31, 33</item>

        <item>This is the sacrament that follows Baptism as part of the initiation process with God and the Church, where the candidate receives the gift of the Holy Spirit and continues their journey with Christ. During Confirmation, the candidate is anointed on the forehead with chrism by a bishop. Since baptism typically happens when the candidate is a baby, confirmation is a great way for an older child to acknowledge that they still want to continue their journey with God and grow their relationship with Him. Celebrate your child’s confirmation by giving them a Bible with meaningful verses highlighted or cross as a daily reminder of God’s love.

Have I not commanded you? Be strong and courageous. Do not be terrified; do not be discouraged, for the Lord your God will be with you wherever you go. Joshua 1:9
For God so loved the world, that he gave his only Son, that whoever believes in him should not perish but have eternal life. John 3:16
When Jesus spoke again to the people, he said, “I am the light of the world. Whoever follows me will never walk in darkness, but will have the light of life.” John 8:12</item>
        <item>\t\t</item>
        <item>\t\t</item>
        <item>\t\t</item>
        <item>\t\t</item>
        <item>\t\t</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>