<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="saints_prayers">
        <item>Prayer to Saint Christopher</item>
        <item>A prayer to Saint Padre Pio</item>
        <item>Prayer to Saint Joseph</item>
        <item>Prayer to Saint Jude</item>
        <item>Prayer to Saint Philomena</item>
        <item>Novena to Saint Philomena</item>
        <item>St. Gertrude Prayer</item>
        <item>Prayer to Saint John Bosco</item>
        <item>Angel of God</item>
        <item>To Saint Gabriel the Archangel</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_of_saints_prayers">
        <item>\t\tFather, grant that I may be a bearer of Christ Jesus, Your Son.
Allow me to warm the often cold,
impersonal scene of modern life with Your burning love.
Strengthen me by Your Holy Spirit
to carry out my mission of changing the world
or some definite part of it for the better.
Despite my lamentable failures,
bring home to me that my advantages
are Your blessings to be shared with others.
Make me more energetic in setting right
what I find wrong with the world instead of complaining about it.
Nourish in me a practical desire to build up
rather than tear down,
to reconcile instead of polarize,
to go out on a limb rather than crave security.
Never let me forget that it is far better to light one candle
than to curse the darkness,
and to join my light, one day, with Yours. Amen.</item>
        <item>\t\tO God,
You gave Saint Pio of Pietrelcina,
Capuchin priest,
the great privilege of participating
in a unique way in the passion of Your Son,
grant me
through his intercession
the grace of … which I ardently desire;
and above all grant me the grace of
living in conformity
with the death of Jesus,
to arrive at the glory
of the resurrection.
Glory be to the Father… (three times)</item>
        <item>\t\t\To you, O blessed Joseph,
do we come in our tribulation,
and having implored the help of your most holy Spouse,
we confidently invoke your patronage also.
Through that charity which bound you
to the Immaculate Virgin Mother of God
and through the paternal love
with which you embraced the Child Jesus,
we humbly beg you graciously to regard the inheritance
which Jesus Christ has purchased by his Blood,
and with your power and strength to aid us in our necessities.

O most watchful guardian of the Holy Family,
defend the chosen children of Jesus Christ;
O most loving father, ward off from us
every contagion of error and corrupting influence;
O our most mighty protector, be kind to us
and from heaven assist us in our struggle
with the power of darkness.
As once you rescued the Child Jesus from deadly peril,
so now protect God\'s Holy Church
from the snares of the enemy and from all adversity;
shield, too, each one of us by your constant protection,
so that, supported by your example and your aid,
we may be able to live piously, to die in holiness,
and to obtain eternal happiness in heaven.

Amen.</item>
        <item>\t\tMost holy Apostle, St. Jude, faithful servant and friend of Jesus, the Church honors and invokes you universally,
            as the patron of difficult cases, of things almost despaired of, Pray for me, I am so helpless and alone.
Intercede with God for me that He bring visible and speedy help where help is almost despaired of.
            Come to my assistance in this great need that I may receive the consolation and help of heaven in all my necessities, tribulations, and sufferings, particularly -
(make your request here)
- and that I may praise God with you and all the saints forever. I promise, O Blessed St. Jude, to be ever mindful of this great favor granted me by God and to always honor you as my special and powerful patron, and to gratefully encourage devotion to you.
Amen

PRAYER

May the Most Sacred Heart of Jesus be adored, and loved in all the tabernacles until the end of time. Amen.

May the most Sacred Heart of Jesus be praised and glorified now and forever. Amen

St. Jude pray for us and hear our prayers. Amen.</item>
        <item>\t\t O Saint Philomena, Virgin and Martyr, whom God glorifies by so many miracles,
            whom the Vicar of Jesus Christ has named the Protectress of The Living Rosary and the Children of Mary, manifest, more and more plainly from the heights of Heaven,
            that a voice holy as thine cannot be denied and that we have the right to rely upon thine aid.
            Obtain for us the grace to be faithful to Jesus Christ, even to death. Amen.</item>

        <item>\t\t We beseech Thee, O Lord, to grant us the pardon of our sins by the intercession of Saint Philomena,
            virgin and martyr, who was always pleasing in Thy sight by her eminent chastity and by the profession of every virtue. Amen. Illustrious virgin and martyr,
            Saint Philomena, behold me prostrate before the throne whereupon it has pleased the Most Holy Trinity to place thee. Full of confidence in thy protection,
            I entreat thee to intercede for me with God, from the heights of Heaven deign to cast a glance upon thy humble client! Spouse of Christ, sustain me in suffering,
            fortify me in temptation, protect me in the dangers surrounding me, obtain for me the graces necessary to me, and in particular (Here specify your request).
            Above all, assist me at the hour of my death. Saint Philomena, powerful with God, pray for us. Amen. O God,
            Most Holy Trinity, we thank Thee for the graces Thou didst bestow upon the Blessed Virgin Mary, and upon Thy handmaid Philomena,
            through whose intercession we implore Thy Mercy. Amen.</item>

        <item>\t\tO most holy angel of God, appointed by God to be my guardian, I give you thanks for all the benefits which you have ever bestowed on me in body and in soul.
            I praise and glorify you that you condescended to assist me with such patient fidelity, and to defend me against all the assaults of my enemies.
            Blessed be the hour in which you were assigned me for my guardian, my defender and my patron. In acknowledgement and return for all your loving ministries to me,
            I offer you the infinitely precious and noble heart of Jesus, and firmly purpose to obey you henceforward, and most faithfully to serve my God. Amen.</item>
        <item>\t\tO glorious Saint John Bosco, who in order to lead young people to the feet of the divine Master and to mould them in the light of faith and Christian morality
            didst heroically sacrifice thyself to the very end of thy life
            and didst set up a proper religious Institute destined to endure and to bring to the farthest boundaries of the earth thy glorious work, obtain also for us
            from Our Lord a holy love for young people who are exposed to so many seductions in order that we may generously spend ourselves in supporting them against the
            snares of the devil,
            in keeping them safe from the dangers of the world, and in guiding them, pure and holy, in the path that leads to God. Amen.</item>
        <item>\t\tO Angel of God, my Guardian Angel, to whom God\'s love commit me here ever this day (or night) be by my side, to light and guide, to rule and guard me. Amen</item>
        <item>\t\tO Blessed Archangel Gabriel, we beseech thee, do thou intercede for us at the throne of divine Mercy in our present necessities,
            that as thou didst announce to Mary the mystery of the Incarnation,
            so through thy prayers and patronage in heaven we may obtain the benefits of the same, and sing the praise of God forever in the land of the living. Amen.</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>